<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info>
    <id>passwords</id>
    <name>Passwords</name>
    <description>This is a Password Manager for viewing, editing and generating passwords. 

        You can insert and import your own passwords or randomly generate new ones. Some characters are excluded upon password generation for readability purposes (1, I, l and B, 8 and o, O, 0). Passwords are stored into the ownCloud database with combined EtM (Encrypt-then-MAC) and MCRYPT_BLOWFISH encryption (read Security part in Documentation for details). 

        Important: passwords can only be read (decrypted) by the user who created the password, on the ownCloud-instance where the password was created in (i.e. same password salt in config.php). If you lose the password salt, all passwords of all users are lost and unretrievable.

        NOTE 1: This is primarily intended as a password MANAGER, e.g. for a local ownCloud instance on your own WPA2 protected LAN. If you trust yourself enough as security expert, you can use this app behind an SSL secured server for a neat cloud solution. The app will be blocked (with message) if not accessed thru https, which will result in your passwords not being loaded (decrypted) and shown. To prevent this, use ownClouds own 'Force SSL'-function on the admin page, or use HSTS (HTTP Strict Transport Security) on your server. Also, make sure your server hasn't any kind of vulnerabilities (POODLE, CSRF, XSS, SQL Injection, Privilege Escalation, Remote Code Execution, to name a few).
        
        NOTE 2: Generated passwords are in fact pseudo-generated (i.e. not using atmospheric noise), since only the Javascript Math.random-function is used, of which I think is randomly 'enough'. After generation of different types of characters (your choice to include lowercase, uppercase, numbers and/or reading marks, strength will be calculated), scrambling of these characters is done using the Fisher-Yates shuffle (also known as Knuth, a de-facto unbiased shuffle algorithm). The script for generating passwords can be found in 'apps/passwords/js/script.js'.</description>
    <licence>AGPL</licence>
    <author>Fallon Turner</author>
    <version>8.0.12</version>
    <namespace>Passwords</namespace>
    <category>tool</category>
    <dependencies>
        <owncloud min-version="8" />
        <lib>mcrypt</lib>
    </dependencies>
    <documentation>
		<user>https://github.com/fcturner/passwords/blob/master/README.md</user>
	</documentation>
</info>
